danner.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy and Security - Customer Service - Danner

At Danner.com your privacy is very important to us.

We do not sell, share, rent or trade your electronically provided personal information to others. We understand your concerns about online security and privacy. Here at Danner our goal is to ensure that your personal and payment information remains secure and your privacy is protected.

**Danner Boots  
PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy applies to information Danner learns about or obtains from you when you visit the Site, and does not apply to any other website, whether or not it is affiliated with or linked to this Site. Definitions contained in the Site’s Terms also apply to this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated in and made a part of the Terms. Your access or use of the Site constitutes your legally binding acceptance of and agreement to this Privacy Policy.

The provisions of this Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time in Danner’s sole discretion and as provided by applicable law. Danner will attempt to provide advance notice by posting such changes to the Site at least thirty (30) days prior to implementation, or a shorter period as required by applicable law and/or business conditions. You should check this Privacy Policy frequently for any such changes, but in any case your continued access or use of the Site will constitute acceptance of any modifications. You may “opt-out” of any change as provided below. Danner’s use of information gathered or obtained at any time is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such use.

The Site is not directed at children, and Danner will not knowingly collect any personal information from any person under age 13. Danner complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and does not knowingly permit submission of Personal Information by anyone under 13 years of age. You must be over age 13 to use the Site.

**Controller of Personal Information**  
Any personal information provided to, or collected by Danner through the Site is controlled by Danner

**What We Collect**  
You may review information collected about you via the Site, and delete or modify personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address or home address or telephone number (“Personal Information”) by following our Correct/Update Procedure. This does not apply to information collected by cookies and used internally to recognize you and/or facilitate your visits to the Site, or information we may retain to comply with legal requirements.

Information You Give Us: Danner receives and stores any information you enter on the Site (for example, when you request information or submit comments about our products or when you create you customer account) or provide in any other manner, including via e-mail. This includes your Personal Information. Danner uses the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests for information, improving the services we offer and communicating with you. We may also use feedback in advertising and other publicity for Danner. Of course, you can choose not to provide such information, but then you might not be able to access or use portions of the Site. You are welcome to make such transactions by mail: Danner Boots, 17634 NE Airport Way, Portland OR 97023 or telephone: 800-345-0430.

Automated Information Collection: Danner automatically receives and stores certain types of information whenever you visit the Site, through “cookies” (as defined below). Cookies are used to facilitate your use of the Site. In addition to information you provide, we collect name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the IP address of the computer you are using and the browser and operating system you are using; the date and time you access the Site; and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to the Site. [We use cookies to store visitor’s preferences, and record specific user information on what pages are visited or accessed. We may also customize web page content based on this information]. We use “cookies” to automatically gather some of this information. A cookie is a small text file that the Site sends to your computer to collect information about your activity on the Site. Cookies automatically transmit information to the Site each time your browser requests a page on the Site and the information is and the information is stored to help facilitate your use of the Site the next time you visit. If you do not want to receive cookies from the Site, you can set your browser to not accept cookies, but you may not be able to access or use certain portions of the Site.

Third Party Servers: You may also get cookies from advertisers on the Site sent by third-party servers. This is a standard practice on most websites that include advertising. Danner does not control, and is not responsible for, cookies from our advertisers. If you do not want to receive cookies from the Site, you can set your browser to not accept cookies.

How We Use/Disclose Your Information Danner may, but is not obligated to, retain the content of any e-mails you send or information or data you provide by other means, including your e-mail address and other Personal Information, so that Danner may respond to your requests for information or questions, and comply with any legal requirements.

Danner may use the information you provide and we collect to: · Administer the Site and diagnose problems with our server; · Verify your identity and respond to your requests for information; · If you have given us permission, to provide you with information about the Site and Danner and our products and services; · Facilitate performance by either of us under the Terms and any other agreement you may enter into with Danner; · Comply with applicable laws, statutes or regulations; · Measure the number of visitors to the Site and how the Site is used; · As specifically provided in the Terms and as you may otherwise agree. We may share your Personal Information with our affiliates, parents and subsidiaries, and with third parties who perform services and other functions for Danner, such as administration of the Site or processing purchases and payments. We may also share your information as necessary to comply with applicable law; to enforce the Terms and the Privacy Policy or the rights of Danner or third parties; as specifically provided in our Terms; and/or as you may otherwise agree. In addition, in the event Danner transfers some or all of its assets to another entity, or is acquired by a third party, information will likely be one of the transferred assets, but should remain subject to existing privacy terms as required by applicable law, statute or regulation.

Danner may respond to any subpoena received from a government agency (i.e., the Securities and Exchange Commission or law enforcement agencies) without prior notice to you. Unless prohibited by law or by a court order, we will notify you of any subpoena received from any other party (i.e., for civil litigation) which requires us to disclose your identity, and will wait ten (10) days, or a lesser amount of time as required by the deadline in the subpoena, before providing the information requested by the subpoena.

Danner does not share our visitors’ Personal Information with any third parties, except as necessary for operation of the Site, provision of our services and compliance with legal requirements, and as provided in our Visitor Content Policy [link to that section] or as we may otherwise notify you at the time you provide information.

**Public Forums**

Please remember that information you post to the Website itself, including User Submissions, will be public information, available for access, use and disclosure by other visitors to the Site. Danner has no obligation to monitor, moderate, screen or otherwise be responsible for any content posted by you or any other third party to the Site, or for use or disclosure of such content. YOU SHOULD EXERCISE CAUTION WHEN DECIDING TO DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ON ANY WEBSITE.

**Danner Partner Policy**  
From time to time, Danner may send you email offers or information on behalf of Danner partners. When you “opt-in” to receive these offers, you consent to use of your Personal Information for such emails, and disclosure of your Personal Information to such third party partners.

**Opt In**  
Before we use your email address or other personal information to send you information or otherwise communicate with you, whether on behalf of Danner or our Danner partners, we ask that you indicate you wish to receive such communication by “opting in” to inclusion on our mailing lists. You can “opt in” at the time you register for membership or otherwise provide your contact information, or by sending an email to info@danner.com. By establishing a user account, you “opt in” to receive information about Danner, our products and our business partners. You may also change or revoke your consent or “opt-in” by giving Danner written notice at the above address provided doing so does not breach any legal duty or commitment you may have to Danner. Also, if you do revoke your consent, keep in mind that you will no longer receive information relating to our products and services.

**Lost or Stolen Information**

You must notify Danner promptly if any user name or password that you use on the Website is lost, stolen or used without permission. Upon such notice, Danner may cancel such user name or password and update our records accordingly.

**Correct/Update Procedure**  
If you want to delete or modify your Personal Information from Danner’s records, or opt-out of receiving some or all of the information we may provide, you may do so by: 

  * Sending an email to info@danner.com
  * By mail to the following address:

Danner  
Direct Sales  
17634 NE Airport Way  
Portland, OR 97230

  * By calling the following telephone number: 800-345-0430

Danner reserves the right to verify the identity of any person making such a request; provided that we shall have no liability whatsoever resulting from false or erroneous requests. Personally identifiable information collected and transferred to back-up or archival storage may be retained indefinitely. Danner may also retain information regarding transactions as necessary for our business records, and as required under applicable law.

**Links**  
The Site may contain links to other sites. These links are for the convenience of visitors to the Site only, and Danner makes no representations and has no responsibility or liability whatsoever regarding such other sites, including those sites with which we may have an affiliation. You should review the privacy policies of other sites carefully before providing any information to such sites. Danner is not responsible for the privacy policies or procedures or the content of any other site.

**Security**  
The Site has reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Danner’s control. While we strive to protect your personal information, Danner cannot ensure, and does not warrant, the security of any information. Communication via the Internet is not failsafe, and there is always a possibility that data may be lost, or intercepted by unauthorized parties during such transmission or after receipt by Danner. You agree that Danner shall have no liability whatsoever in connection with such lost or intercepted data. You also agree that, to the extent required by law, we may use your Personal Information in order to notify you of any unauthorized access to your Personal Information of which we become aware.

**Conditions of Use**  
Your access and use of the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms [link] including limitations on damages, and the laws of the State of [Oregon].

**Contacting Danner**  
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, the Terms, or any other questions concerning the Site, please contact:

Danner  
Direct Sales  
17634 NE Airport Way  
Portland, OR 97230   
800-345-0430
